gamelinkexchange.com 2016-03-24

# Privacy Policy For All Services Provided By GameSkip.com

## FAQ

### I don't see any claimed items in my game?

  * When you click any link try to wait untill all the elements of page loads completely. Sometimes you have to click a button to accept it.
  * Try restart your browser.
  * Always use Latest version of Your Browser or try different browser."
  * Try updating your Flash Version, if other options are not working.
  * Try adding more Game Friends in order to claim more.
  * Let us know if any game Bonuses not working, we will try to find any alternative - ADMIN@gameskip.com

### What Should i do when Game Freezes or Hangs or Runs very Slow?

  * Try to restart your browser
  * Try restarting your Computer if it's still not working.
  * Always use Latest version of Your Browser or try different browser."
  * Try updating your Flash Version, OR
  * Try [CCLEANER](http://www.piriform.com/ccleaner) Download it and clean your history and cache. try disable some some unknown startup items and resart your computer after that, OR
  * For Windows Users: Try creating new user in control panel. Then try to play game with new account.
  * Try updating your PC or Buy a new one in the worst case scenario. 

## Privacy Policy

### Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us in all the aspects. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.co.in/policies/technologies/ads/ Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, GameSkip has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### Collection of Personal Information

When visiting GameSkip, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

All information collected through facebook app will be deleted after every month. We don't kept any records and all information collected will be deleted right after one month.

By installing our chrome and mozilla browser extension you are agree that game posts of your and your friends will be collected and stored on website temporary. All Game Posts will be deleted after 3 days - 30 days without any notice automatically from this website.

### Links to Third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and references. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on any of these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own and should proceed accordingly.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. You should check it regularly in order to get familiar with the changed policies.

### Questions

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact us at:

Fastline Products  
6474, Gali Ishwari Prasad  
Bara Hindu Rao  
Delhi 110006  
INDIA  
Email: admin@gameskip.com
